<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Updates on Open Source Foundries, Ltd.</title>
    <link>https://opensourcefoundries.github.io/osfoundries-rendered/categories/updates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Updates on Open Source Foundries, Ltd.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017, Open Source Foundries, Ltd.; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 13:50:46 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://opensourcefoundries.github.io/osfoundries-rendered/categories/updates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>microPlatform update 0.4</title>
      <link>https://opensourcefoundries.github.io/osfoundries-rendered/blog/2017/12/13/blog-post-update-0.4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://opensourcefoundries.github.io/osfoundries-rendered/blog/2017/12/13/blog-post-update-0.4/</guid>
      <description>Zephyr microPlatform Highlights  Zephyr tree based on v1.10  Components MCUBoot Features  Not addressed in this update  Bugs  Not addressed in this update  Zephyr Features  Not addressed in this update  Bugs Bluetooth fixes:  Notable fixes include over ten patches to Bluetooth Mesh, along with two fixes to the core BT controller code.  CMake fixes:  The CMake build system received several fixes for various issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>microPlatform update 0.3</title>
      <link>https://opensourcefoundries.github.io/osfoundries-rendered/blog/2017/12/07/blog-post-update-0.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://opensourcefoundries.github.io/osfoundries-rendered/blog/2017/12/07/blog-post-update-0.3/</guid>
      <description>Zephyr microPlatform Highlights  Zephyr tree from 1.10 release candidate, with CMake MCUBoot and FOTA sample build systems ported to CMake  Components MCUBoot Features CMake-based build system:  The Zephyr build system was rewritten to use cmake instead of Kbuild, following the equivalent upstream change.  Bugs Fix jump to invalid target when not validating slot 0:  A bug fix to the core bootloader was merged which affects configurations that do not validate slot 0 before booting into it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>microPlatform update 0.2</title>
      <link>https://opensourcefoundries.github.io/osfoundries-rendered/blog/2017/11/16/blog-post-update-0.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://opensourcefoundries.github.io/osfoundries-rendered/blog/2017/11/16/blog-post-update-0.2/</guid>
      <description>Zephyr microPlatform Highlights  Final Zephyr commit before the build system moves to CMake MCUBoot memory and flash space optimizations  Components MCUBoot Features Simulator tests rewritten in Cargo test format:  &amp;ldquo;The simulator tests have been rewritten to use Rust&amp;rsquo;s native testing framework. Users can run the tests by running \&amp;ldquo;cargo test\&amp;rdquo; from the sim/ directory.&amp;rdquo;  mbedTLS memory allocator:  The Zephyr port now uses a memory allocator from mbedTLS, which provides some memory and flash savings over the native Zephyr allocator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>microPlatform update 0.1</title>
      <link>https://opensourcefoundries.github.io/osfoundries-rendered/blog/2017/11/09/blog-post-update-0.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://opensourcefoundries.github.io/osfoundries-rendered/blog/2017/11/09/blog-post-update-0.1/</guid>
      <description>Zephyr microPlatform Highlights  Zephyr tree from 1.10 development cycle, before CMake transition MCUBoot tree following the 1.0.0 release Fixes and other improvements to sample applications  Components MCUBoot Features  Not addressed in this update  Bugs  Not addressed in this update  Zephyr Features GPIO interface deprecations:  The GPIO_PIN_ENABLE and GPIO_PIN_DISABLE configuration constants, which overlap with functionality provided by the pinux driver, were deprecated.  New CoAP API:  There is a new CoAP API; the existing API has been deprecated.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>